Hello everyone friends,
this change has been
updated in the already open app which is going to open from 22nd,
you guys can try it from tonight, I will
show you its procedure, let's
start the video, before starting the video, a
small request to you guys, please
subscribe my channel, support me, first of all our
Ola Electric app, the app in which
we booked the scooter, is
not the app, our operating app,
go to its support,
there you see the man's symbol, choose the
last option,
after going to support, you will see an option, it is
given completely here, if you have any
problem with it, you can see it here,
friend, I have chatted with you about the upgrade,
he had told you this completely, it means
your registration will start from 22nd and it has been
updated in the already open,
maybe from 12:00 tonight or tomorrow morning from
8:00, you guys can register from here,
so everyone has to make this change
in the starting which I had already told you  Those who are
within the 40 km surrounding area, first 20
km, then it will change for those within 40 km,
after that it will
change for those far away, one condition has also been kept in this that after
registering with the charge number, we will have to go to
Scotro Lake
and come back to the lake and we are talking about Care
Plus, so whichever plane you have taken or you are
not going to give us any charge, that
means there will be no dropping, we can take ourselves and
do it comfortably by giving our time, if
everyone wants to do it then they should do it, when it is being
given for free then it is better
than the previous one, a lot of things have been tested in news suspension,
I have also posted a video yesterday, if
you want you
can watch it from there, it was a
small information like how I take the penis
and after uploading a video,
I will update you, that is, how to register,
let's meet again in the next video, hello
everyone, thank you